FIROZA PARMAR

90233 60056



firozaparmar786@gmail.com



Baghdadi Gate, Rajkot



SUMMARY

I am an experienced and certified high school teacher with over 25 years of experience teaching in diverse elementary classroom settings. Effective communicator proficient in developing and delivering lesson plans that emphasize Common Core Standards, and positive results. I am able to act as a facilitator of powerful learning experiences, while allowing students to dictate certain lessons and lead with curiosity.

EDUCATION

TEACHER

SWAMINARAYAN GURUKUL

D.EL.ED /PTC 2011 - 2013

GODHANIYA GIRLS' COLLEGE

BA WITH ENGLISH 2022-Present

SKILLS

- Strong organizational and timemanagement skills
- Exceptional communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ENGLISH TUTOR

SIGMA EDUCATIONAL NETWORK | 2018-2023 CITY: PORBANDAR

ENGLISH TUTOR

SARASWATI SCHOOLING SYSTEM | 2023- Present CITY: RAJKOT

TUTOR

VJM GIRLS' SCHOOL | 1997- 2018 CITY: PORBANDAR

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH HINDI URDU GUJARATI